<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on BrandFourFive Blog</title>
    <link>https://blog.brandfourfive.com/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on BrandFourFive Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Code released under the Apache 2.0 license.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 12 May 2020 11:52:45 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://blog.brandfourfive.com/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>A BRIEF GUIDE ON TikTok MARKETING</title>
      <link>https://blog.brandfourfive.com/posts/a-brief-guide-on-tiktok-marketing/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 May 2020 11:52:45 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.brandfourfive.com/posts/a-brief-guide-on-tiktok-marketing/</guid>
      <description>A brief guide on TikTok marketing. At a time when building a community is most important, TikTok has shown itself as a perfect place to increase your brand awareness. TikTok has over 800 million monthly active users and an average view time of 52 minutes, which gives your brand enough show time. TikTok is the first video sharing network that appeal to GenZ users, which is best known for viral dance trends, challenges and lip-sync videos.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WHAT ARE YOUR CUSTOMERS PAINPOINTS? 5 KEY WAYS TO FIND OUT</title>
      <link>https://blog.brandfourfive.com/posts/what-are-your-customers-painpoints/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 May 2020 11:52:45 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.brandfourfive.com/posts/what-are-your-customers-painpoints/</guid>
      <description>What are my customers&amp;#39; pain points? One crucial question every business leader must ask. You probably think that you have your customers&amp;#39; challenges all figured out. But what you have failed to consider is that your customers need different solutions for different problems per time; they probably want you to solve problem A, right now and not problem C.
Your customers&amp;#39; pain points are the challenges they experience, which is an opportunity for your business to make better solutions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BE the NO 1 on YOUR CUSTOMERS MIND in 5 WAYS</title>
      <link>https://blog.brandfourfive.com/posts/be-the-no-1-on-your-customers-mind-in-5-ways/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2019 16:47:32 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.brandfourfive.com/posts/be-the-no-1-on-your-customers-mind-in-5-ways/</guid>
      <description>{{ with .Resources.ByType &amp;ldquo;image_1_brandFourFive&amp;rdquo; }} {{ end }}
Want a smartphone? What is the first phone brand that comes in mind?. Movie? What comes to mind first? Taxi? What comes to mind? Online retailers? When you need a product or service, there&amp;rsquo;s always going to be a first answer. This simply answer is that brand that has become top notch in your mind.
Then the big question, is yours on their mind?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CONTENT CURATORS. YOU WANT TO BUY BENZ? THEN YOU NEED THESE TOOLS</title>
      <link>https://blog.brandfourfive.com/posts/content-curators/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2019 20:54:45 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.brandfourfive.com/posts/content-curators/</guid>
      <description>These content tools are here to stay, it would definitely make your work easy and very professional, so you need to keep them handy&amp;hellip;
ANIMAKER
You nerd a studio created animated video without outrageous price tag? Then, you need ANIMAKER. You can create multiple video types including explainer videos, white board videos and even infographic videos.
All you need to do is to sign up, and viola! Lots of templates to work with and you can create yours too!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>